<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="${descVersion}">
	<author>${author}</author>
	<version>${version}</version>
	<title>
		<en>${title}</en>
	</title>
	<description>
		<en>
			<![CDATA[
This mod allows you to outsource jobs for which you don't have the time or equipment to contractors.
The cost of the work will vary mainly according to the time it takes, if you have few money to spend you can be satisfied with contracts done in more time, while if you urgently need the work to be completed you will have to spend a little more.
Press CTRL + SHIFT + C to open the contractors management panel.

Types of jobs currently available:
 - Plowing
 - Cultivating
 - Sowing
 - Subsoiling
 - Lime spreading
 - Selling goods
]]>
		</en>
		<de>
			<![CDATA[
Dieser Mod ermöglicht es Ihnen, Arbeiten, für die Sie keine Zeit oder Ausrüstung haben, an Auftragnehmer auszulagern.
Die Kosten für die Arbeit variieren hauptsächlich nach der benötigten Zeit. Wenn Sie wenig Geld zur Verfügung haben, können Sie mit Aufträgen zufrieden sein, die in mehr Zeit erledigt werden, während Sie, wenn Sie die Arbeit dringend benötigen, etwas mehr ausgeben müssen.
Drücken Sie STRG + UMSCHALT + C, um die Auftragnehmerverwaltung zu öffnen.

Derzeit verfügbare Auftragsarten:
 - Pflügen
 - Kultivieren
 - Säen
 - Unterpflügen
 - Kalk streuen
 - Verkaufen
]]>
		</de>
		<fr>
			<![CDATA[
Ce mod vous permet de confier à des entrepreneurs les travaux pour lesquels vous n'avez pas le temps ou l'équipement nécessaire.
Le coût du travail varie principalement en fonction du temps qu'il prend. Si vous avez peu d'argent à dépenser, vous pouvez vous contenter de contrats réalisés en plus de temps, tandis que si vous avez besoin d'un travail urgent, vous devrez dépenser un peu plus.
Appuyez sur CTRL + SHIFT + C pour ouvrir le panneau de gestion des entrepreneurs.

Types de travaux actuellement disponibles :
 - Labourer
 - Cultiver
 - Semer
 - Décompacter
 - Épandage de chaux
 - Vente de produits
]]>
		</fr>
	</description>
	<multiplayer supported="true" />
	<iconFilename>icon.png</iconFilename>

	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="rmod/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="utility/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="fieldStatusUtil.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="callContractors.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="playerExtension.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="contractsManager/contractsManager.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="gui/ccGui.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="gui/ccGuiSigningContractsLocker.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>

	<actions>
		<action name="CALL_CONTRACTORS_SHOW" axisType="HALF" />
	</actions>

	<inputBinding>
		<actionBinding action="CALL_CONTRACTORS_SHOW">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lshift KEY_c" />
		</actionBinding>
	</inputBinding>

	<l10n filenamePrefix="translations/l10n" />

</modDesc>
